http://www.boydandco.com.au/pages/privacy-policy

View all results
(0)
Home /
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Boyd & Co uses and protects any information that you provide us with while using this website. Boyd & Co is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. If we ask you to provide certain information to help identify you while using this website, you can be assured that the information will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Boyd & Co may make changes to this privacy policy from time to time by updating the page here. To ensure you remain informed about our current policy, please remember to check this page often as you visit the website.
What we collect
We may collect the following information: Name and job title Contact information, including email address Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better overall service, and specifically for the following reasons: Internal record keeping To improve our products and services To periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes, which may be via email, phone, fax or mail The information may be used to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that the information you provide us with remains secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have established relevant physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file, which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Boyd & Co, uses cookies on our website to allow us to recall your preferences when you re-visit us. This is common practice on most websites that you visit. You can choose to turn off cookies in your browser settings; however, this will mean that some of our website functions may not be available to you. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This information helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and tailor it to each of our customer’s needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and once completed the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, we no longer have control over those websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required to do so by law. We may use your personal information to send promotions to you about third parties, which we believe may be of interest to you. We will only do this if you grant us permission. If you believe that any information held by us about you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us at the above address. We will promptly correct any errors that you inform us of.
Close
